secure-tunnel.com 2006-06-18

# Secure-Tunnel. Safe and Secure Servers.

|  |  | 

**Privacy Policy**  
---  
  
At Secure-Tunnel.com, we are in the business of protecting your online privacy and security, and we take our job very seriously. We will always keep your personal information confidential. Please take a moment to read the following policy to learn how we handle your personal information. **Personal information**  
Secure-Tunnel.com will NEVER sell or trade your personal information. This means no company will ever contact you on our behalf, nor will your name or email be placed on any mailing lists. We do not enjoy receiving Spam, and assume you do not either, so it is our corporate policy never to reveal your email address to any third party. **Why do we collect this information**  
Secure-Tunnel collects your personal information to ensure your account will not be used as an agent for spamming, hacking or anything else outlined in our TOS. We also use this information to give you superior customer service, to provide you with convenient access to our services, and to continue developing solutions that meet the ongoing and changing needs of our customers. In addition, we use your personal information to keep you up to date on the latest special offers, service announcements, software updates, and other security related information you may be interested in.  
  
**How we protect your personal information**  
Secure-Tunnel safeguards the security of the data you send us with physical, electronic, and managerial procedures. We use the latest in encryption technologies; utilizing a 128-bit SSL certificate on our site anywhere your personal information is transmitted or viewable. You may verify our SSL certificate any time with Verisign by clicking on the secure seal in the signup area.

No matter where you go on the Internet we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data. Change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure browser.   
**  
Our companywide commitment to privacy **  
To make sure your personal information remains confidential, we communicate these privacy guidelines to every Secure-Tunnel employee.

Secure-Tunnel does not knowingly solicit personal information from children or send them requests for personal information.

Secure-Tunnel website contains links to other sites. Secure-Tunnel does not share your personal information with those websites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies.  
  
_Before purchasing any plan, please read the_ _Terms & Conditions. _
